ALICE LEE

Professional and courteous hotel bilingual front desk clerk with 8+ years of experience in the hospitality industry. Skilled at handling a variety of administrative tasks while providing optimal customer service to ensure smooth hotel operations. Works well under pressure while maintaining a positive and friendly attitude.

1 Main Street, Newport Beach, CA 09876 alee@youremail.com (123) 456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FRONT DESK CLERK

Milton Grand Hotel, Los Angeles, CA December 2014 - Present

- Manages front desk for a 600-room full-service four-diamond hotel
- Greets and assists all guests with enthusiasm and professional demeanor
- ♦ Checks guests in and out of rooms with speed and accuracy
- ♦ Works with housekeeping staff to ensure all rooms are cleaned and ready on time
- Ensures transportation of guests on the hotel shuttle to and from the hotel
- ♦ Fluent in English and Spanish

FRONT DESK CLERK

Embassy Express Suites, Los Angeles, CA October2012 - December 2014

- Handled front desk operations for 250-room hotel
- · Took reservations and checked guests in and out
- Provided information to hotel guests regardingdining, nearby attractions, amenities, and available rooms

EDUCATION

Associate Degree in Hospitality Management

Glendale Community College, Glendale, CA Septem be r 2010 - Ju ne 2012

High School Diploma

Newport High School, Newport Beach, CA September2006 - May 2010

KEY SKILLS

- O utstand i n g com m u n i catio n ski lls
- ♦ Excellent organizational ability
- ♦ Adept at conflict resolution
- Reliable, flexible, and a good problem solver

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified Front Desk Representative (CFDR),AHLEI,2016